timesplus.co.uk 2019-06-30

# News UK - Privacy Policy

This Privacy and Cookie Policy (this Policy) explains how we collect, use, share, disclose or otherwise process personal information we hold about you. Understanding what our audiences prefer allows us to personalise content, show relevant adverts, and generally improve your experience of our products and services.

News Corp UK & Ireland Limited and its subsidiary companies listed below (together "News UK", "we", "our" or "us") will collect, use, share and disclose or otherwise process your personal information in line with this Policy. The relevant data controller for your data will depend on which product or service you have interacted with or to which title you have subscribed as set out below.

**News Group Newspapers Limited**  
The Sun, The Sun on Sunday, The Irish Sun, The Scottish Sun, The Irish Sun on Sunday, The Scottish Sun on Sunday and the associated websites.

**News Promotions Limited**  
The Sun's Dream Team Fantasy Football and the associated websites.

**Times Newspapers Limited**  
The Times, The Sunday Times and The Sunday Times Travel Magazine and the associated websites.

**Newsprinters Limited**  
Direct to Consumer, Direct to Retail and other production and retail services

**The Times Literary Supplement Limited**  
The Times Literary Supplement and the associated websites.

**Sunday Times Driving Limited**  
Sunday Times Driving Limited

**News UK & Ireland Limited**   
The Quiz App   
The influencer talent agency trading as The Fifth and the associated websites   

**talkSPORT Limited**  
For the national radio stations talkSPORT, talkSPORT 2, talkRADIO and Virgin Radio UK, and the local radio stations Scottish Sun 80s, Scottish Sun Hits, and Scottish Sun Greatest Hits

**U105 Limited**  
For U105, broadcasting on 105.8FM and DAB in Northern Ireland and associated websites.

**The Internet Business Limited**  
(Trading as Tibus) providers of digital infrastructure services.

**Simply Zesty UK Limited**  
(Trading as Zesty) a PR and digital social media agency operating in the UK.

**Independent Broadcasting Corporation Limited**  
For LMFM in Drogheda

**Capital Radio Productions Limited**  
For FM 104 in Dublin.

**Treaty Radio Limited**  
For Live 95FM in Limerick.

**City Broadcasting Limited**  
For Q102 in Dublin.

**Cork Media Enterprises Limited**  
For 96FM and C103 in Cork.

  * You can find out more about how and when collect your personal information.

We collect information about you when you provide it to us: for example, when you fill out our online forms, subscribe to one of our titles, enter a competition being run on one of our radio stations, respond to our promotions, call or text in to the radio studio, register and use one of our apps, enquire about our products and services or participate in a reader forum (which could be on any medium). We may record phone calls or customer enquiries via online chat for quality, training and management purposes.

We also collect information automatically when you interact with our websites or use our apps. This can include information about your device, including its Advertising ID (e.g. Google's Advertiser Identification or Apple's Identifier for Advertisers) and general geographic location. This can be to provide services that have copyright restrictions, to deliver news that is relevant to where you are, tailor advertising to your interests and provide a better experience . We may also collect information from cookies placed on your device. See the section on Cookies for more information about our use of cookies. With your consent, we may also collect the specific location of your device or request access to data from other applications to provide certain services you have requested.

If you log in to our websites or online services through a third party site, such as Facebook, that site may pass information to us, such as user ID, name associated with the ID, email address and location, plus other information permitted under the privacy policy for that website. Our websites and apps may also return information about you to that social networking site regarding your log in, such as which News UK websites and apps you visit and your use of the social media services on those websites and apps.

If you log in with or connect to your account using social media (Facebook, Twitter, etc), the social media service's use of the shared information will be governed by their privacy policy. If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with your News UK account, and do not participate in social sharing on our websites or apps.

If you correspond with any of our titles or radio stations, or interact with other customers or audience members or our staff, for example by using polls, comments, text messages, video, email, phone, radio or by post, we may display this content indefinitely in any relevant context, subject to our editorial judgement and your rights as set out in this Policy. This may be anonymised in the case of testimonials or customer service conversations.

If you take part in any reader or listener forums, send us letters for publication, or take part in any radio 'phone-ins', then you may be identifiable to others publicly and your comments attributed to you.

Any information about yourself or others that you post on our social media pages, on platforms like Twitter, Facebook and other chat rooms, blogs and forums, will be viewed by others (including search engines), over whom we have no control. You are responsible for the information you choose to post or otherwise make available in such public areas, and you acknowledge that this may be collected and used by third parties.

We use Experian to make the content and advertising shown on devices that you might use or that may relate to the same household more relevant and useful. Experian may also provide insight reporting as part of their service. As part of this process Experian uses cookies and may receive information about the kind of device you use as well as your IP address, location data, device user agent string or information about websites where your device has previously displayed advertising. By using our sites, you acknowledge that Experian will process personal data about you for the above purpose and for the profiling of audiences bearing similarities to your data on the basis of our or their legitimate interests. You have a choice about whether or not you want your information to be used in this way and you can set your preferences by visiting [www.experianmarketingservices.digital/cookieoptout](https://www.experianmarketingservices.digital/cookieoptout). This won't stop you from seeing content about our products and services when you visit our websites, but it will mean that the content you do see may not be as relevant to you.

Our use of Acxiom (a database marketing company): If you have a subscription to one of our titles, or use one of our products or services, we may check with Acxiom to see if they have any relevant lifestyle and demographic insight information about you. This helps us make sure that our marketing is more relevant to you. This is only where you have provided permission or there is a legitimate interest for Acxiom and us to do this. Where we receive information from Acxiom, we use it in accordance with this Policy and the law. You have control over how that information is used. For more information on Acxiom and the data they provide, and to opt-out of their program, please [www.acxiom.co.uk](https://www.acxiom.co.uk/).

We may also obtain online and offline information about you from other organisations, such as consumer insight providers that have your permission or where there is a legitimate interest in sharing your personal information with us or companies like us. We may combine this with information we collect in accordance with this Policy.

Other organisations that provide products and services to you may also share information with us. For example, they may notify us when you move home or when the payment card you used with us is renewed or replaced, so that we can keep your information accurate and up to date. This also helps ensure that you do not lose access to our products and services.

  * You can find out more about the legal reasons behind our use of your personal information and when they apply.

There may be some uses of your information where we need to ask for your consent. You will have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, however, if you withdraw consent, we may not be able to provide the product or service you have requested.

We also process your personal information in order to fulfil a contract we have with you. For example, we would use your information to provide you with access to your digital subscription or other products you have signed up for or to provide a prize to which you are entitled.

We may use your information where there is a legitimate reason to do so. For example, we may use your information where it would help achieve our business objectives or to facilitate a benefit to you or someone else.

We only rely on legitimate interests if the reason for using your information is fair and lawful. Where we want to rely on legitimate interests as a legal basis, we will carry out a balancing test between our legitimate interests and your privacy rights. Our legitimate interests in processing personal data include:

  * to support a free press, including journalistic activities of societal importance;
  * to support individual and societal rights to receive information;
  * to develop, deliver and maintain relevant and engaging products services and advertising;
  * understanding when our audiences engage with us or other organisations;
  * to build a clearer understanding of who our audiences are in order to better serve them;
  * to carry on the business of a commercial organisation; and
  * to demonstrate that we provide services and products to agreed industry standards.

There may be situations where we need to use your information to comply with legal and regulatory obligations or defend claims. This may include publishing information about prize winners, for example.

In the table below we have listed the main reasons we process your information and the legal bases that are available to us. The specific legal basis we use will depend on the activity the information is used for. Please keep in mind that while we will rely on one legal basis, if that is no longer available to us, we may be able to rely on another.

Consent, Fulfil a Contract, Legitimate Interest 

To send you product-related and similar product and services communications 

Fulfil a Contract, Legitimate Interest 

Consent, Legitimate Interest 

Consent, Legitimate Interest 

Fulfil a Contract, Legitimate Interest, Legal Obligation 

Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interest 

Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interest 

Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legal Obligation 

Legitimate Interest, Legal Obligation 

Consent, Legitimate Interest, Legal Obligation 

Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interest, Legal Obligation 

  * You can find out more about how we use your information.

We will use your information to provide you with products and services you have asked for and to manage our relationship with you, including allowing you to interact, comment, and participate in online games, contests and reward programmes.

We may use your information to monitor, improve and protect our products, content, services and websites, both online and offline. We may also provide you with help and support where we believe it is required. For example, if you have provided your contact information, we may contact you when a checkout journey is not completed.

We sometimes make assumptions about your interests based on the way you interact with our products and services and the information we hold about you. For example:

For The Times and The Sunday Times subscribers: If we notice that you regularly read the Business section of The Times website first, then move on to Comments, we may promote articles in those sections or other related content so you get the most out of the product. We might also tailor your Best of Times Bulletins and other communications.

For Sun readers: If we notice that you have previously booked a Holiday for £9.50, we may continue to promote holidays to you in the future based on this information.

For talkSPORT listeners: If we know you are interested in buying a car, we may insert a car advert into a commercial break on the online audio stream you are listening to.

Knowing these preferences also allows us to understand the products, content and services our customers like, letting us focus our efforts on developing those areas. We may also use this information to make decisions about what direct marketing to show you.

If you choose to turn on the "Do Not Track" setting in your browser, your browser sends a special signal to websites, analytics companies, ad networks, plug-in providers, and other web services you encounter while browsing to request that they stop tracking your activity. Currently our websites and apps are not designed to respond to "Do Not Track" signals.

If you correspond with any of our titles or radio stations, or interact with other customers or audience members or our staff, for example by using polls, comments, text messages, video, email, phone, radio or by post, we may display this content indefinitely in any relevant context, subject to our editorial judgement and your rights as set out in this Policy. This may be anonymised in the case of testimonials or customer service conversations.

If you take part in any reader or listener forums, send us letters for publication, or take part in any radio 'phone-ins', then you may be identifiable to others publicly and your comments attributed to you.

Any information about yourself or others that you post on our social media pages, on platforms like Twitter, Facebook and other chat rooms, blogs and forums, will be viewed by others (including search engines), over whom we have no control. You are responsible for the information you choose to post or otherwise make available in such public areas, and you acknowledge that this may be collected and used by third parties.

If you use third party payment providers, such as PayPal, to pay for or receive payment from us that site may pass information to us including your name, email address, billing or other address, phone number (if applicable), date of sign-up, the number of payments you have received from verified PayPal users, whether you have been verified to have control of a bank account and any other information you agree they can share.

When you visit one of our websites or use one of our apps, advertising networks and other intermediaries select and then display adverts on your device. In the case of some of our radio stations, when listening online, partners insert a relevant audio advert for you to listen to.

  * In this section we explain when and why we share your information with our partners and other organisations.

Your information will be shared between the News UK companies listed in the About Us section above for use in accordance with this Policy. We may share your information with Unruly Group Limited a wholly-owned subsidiary of News UK where there is a legitimate interest in doing so, for use in accordance with their [privacy policy](https://unruly.co/privacy/).

News UK is part of the News Corporation ("News Corp") group of companies and as such, we may rely on our legitimate interests as an organisation that operates an advertising funded business model, to share your information with [News Corp and its affiliates](https://newscorp.com/about/our-businesses/) to:

  * perform analytics and analysis of how you interact with the group's products and services, to facilitate business efficiencies and develop products and services that would be relevant to you; and
  * deliver more relevant advertising from across our News Corp network.

If you would like to opt-out of this sharing or exercise your data protection rights, you can email [dataprotection@news.co.uk](mailto:dataprotection@news.co.uk) but please bear in mind that opting-out will relate to any future sharing and not to information already shared. For more information about how to exercise your rights, please see the section on Access & Control. Opting-out may also mean you do not receive the best experience across News Corp products, services and websites.

Where your information is used for advertising purposes, you will be provided with information about how it is used and be able to control what information is used and how, as well as with which affiliates it is shared.

These affiliates may be located inside or outside of the EEA, including the United States of America. We have appropriate agreements in place to ensure they protect your information in accordance with our legal obligations.

We also participate in an advertising platform offered by our affiliate, NC Audience Exchange LLC, called News IQ. To learn more about News Corp Connect please visit <http://ncaudienceexchange.com/about/>.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties, such as competition partners, for their direct marketing purposes where we have told you about this and you have given permission or there is a legitimate interest to do so.

We may share your personal information with our partners who operate products and services using our brands where you use these services. This includes partners such as The Sun Bingo, The Times Currency Services, The Sunday Times Wine Club and Sun Bets. We will only share your information where we have an appropriate agreement in place with the partner. The information we share will be used in accordance with our partner's privacy policy, which you should read when you sign up with the partner.

These partners will also pass us the information they collect about you, including your usage and interaction with those products and services, which we will use in accordance with this Policy.

We may pass your information to our processors – companies that we use to provide services on our behalf, for example for home delivery services, prize fulfilment agencies, market research or other purposes mentioned in this Policy. These processors can only use your information in accordance with our instructions and for no other purpose.

When you complete our registration forms or use our services, we may transfer your information to our group companies and processors outside the EEA to countries that may not have data protection rules that provide the same level of protection. However, we only transfer your information where there are appropriate measures and controls in place. If you would like to receive a copy of the applicable data transfer safeguards used when your information is transferred outside the EEA to non-adequate countries, please contact us at [dataprotection@news.co.uk](mailto:dataprotection@news.co.uk).

If we sell part or all of our business, customer information may be one of the transferred business assets. If this happens, your information may be disclosed to any successors of our business for them to use for the purpose set out in this Policy.

  * You can find out more about what your data protection rights are and how you can exercise them.

Please ensure you update your personal information or tell us if it changes or is inaccurate. You can update your details, for example your email address, in your account settings or an equivalent section if you are a subscriber. You may also email our Customer Services team at [info@news.co.uk](mailto:info@news.co.uk).

You can change your mind about receiving direct marketing or other communications you receive from us, such as bulletins and other information about your chosen products and services (for example, your Times+ subscription or one of our campaigns) by contacting us using the details below, changing the settings in your preference centre or by following the unsubscribe instructions in the relevant communication.

There may be some types of communication that you receive that cannot be controlled through your preference centre, but you will still be able to opt-out by following the instructions in the communication itself.

Where we may rely on your consent to process personal information, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Often, this can be managed through the preference centre – such as your consent for us to send you communications. Otherwise, please contact us at [dataprotection@news.co.uk](mailto:dataprotection@news.co.uk) with details of your request. In some instances we may still have an alternative legal basis to continue to process that personal information and we will inform you of that. If you do withdraw consent we may not be able to provide the product or service you have requested.

You may request a copy of your personal information from any News UK company which may hold personal information about you. You can also ask us to correct any inaccuracies in your personal information. In some circumstances you may be able to ask us to transfer information you have provided to us to another organisation. Similarly, you may be able to transfer your information from another organisation to us, but you should check with us first if this is possible.

You may also have the right to object, erase, or restrict our processing of your information – for example, where we process personal data because this is in our legitimate interests, you may object to this. We will need to carefully consider your request, as there may be circumstances which require us, or allow us, to continue processing your data.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [dataprotection@news.co.uk](mailto:dataprotection@news.co.uk). These rights may be restricted by law, for example we may not be able to provide a copy of your data where the data we hold is also the data of a third party and it is not reasonable to disclose this information.

We will retain your information for as long as necessary for the uses set out in this Policy, or while there is a legitimate reason for doing so. If you ask us to delete your information before that time, we may not be able to do so due to technical, legal, regulatory or contractual constraints. For example, we would need to retain your name and contact details for suppression purposes if you do not want to receive direct marketing from us.

If you ask for your account to be closed, we will do this as soon as is reasonably possible subject to any applicable terms and conditions relating to the account. Personal information from closed accounts is retained in order to comply with legal obligations, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed and to resolve disputes.

  * You can find out more about the cookies we use and why. You can also find out more about how to control them.

Cookies and other online tracking technologies are small bits of data or code that are used to identify your devices when you use and interact with our websites and other services. They are often used for remembering your preferences, to identify popular news stories, to remember you're logged in and allowing you to comment on stories.

Our legal bases for cookies and similar technologies Placing cookies: in order to place cookies, tags and other technologies on your browser or device, we need to have your permission. We do this by providing a clear notice in the form of a cookie banner that tells you what cookies are used for, as well as providing you with useful information about the technologies we use and a link to this Policy. You'll need to indicate your acceptance of our use of cookies. On a mobile device this might be by swiping a banner, pressing a button, or using facial recognition.

You are able to opt-out of the use of cookies. For more information, see the section on Managing Cookies.

Using information collected from cookies: where we want to use the information that cookies and similar technologies collect, we either need your consent or a legitimate interest.

**Essential Cookies and Similar Technologies**

These are vital for the running of our services on our websites and apps. Without the use of these cookies, parts of our websites would not function. For example, Times+ uses cookies to help us identify which of our readers have a subscription in order to access content they are entitled to on the website. We use these cookies to tell if you're logged in to your account, which allows extra functionality, such as commenting on stories.

 **Analytics Cookies and Similar Technologies**

These collect information about your use of our websites and apps, and enable us to improve the way they work. For example, analytics cookies show us which are the most frequently visited pages on The Sun or The Times websites allowing us to provide the most popular news articles further up the page. They help us record how you interact with our websites, such as how you navigate around pages and from page to page, identifying improvements we can make to the customer journey. They also help identify any difficulties you have accessing our services, so we can fix any problems. Additionally, these cookies allow us to see overall patterns of usage at an aggregated level.

We may place cookies and similar technologies on behalf of comScore who help us measure the size and quality of our audiences across platforms. You can learn more and control how comScore use your information here <http://www.scorecardresearch.com/preferences.aspx>.

 **Functional/Preference Cookies and Similar Technologies**

These cookies collect information about your choices and preferences, and allow us to remember things like language, your username (so you can log in faster), text size, and location, so we can show you relevant content to where you are. They allow us to customise the services you have accessed. We also use these cookies to provide you with services such as video clips.

 **Tracking, Advertising Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We use these types of technologies to provide advertisements that we think may be more relevant to your interests. This can be done by delivering online adverts based on your previous web browsing activity, known as "online behavioural advertising" (OBA). Cookies are placed on your browser which will remember the websites you have visited. Adverts based on what you have been looking at are then displayed to you when you visit websites which use the same advertising networks.

For example, you may be doing online research to buy a bicycle, and read several articles about bikes on various websites. As you browse those sites a cookie from an advertising network would be placed in your browser. It would remember that you had visited several websites related to cycling. Then, when you visited another website in the same advertising network, the website could show you an advert related to cycling.

We may also use cookies and similar technologies to provide you with adverts based on your location, offers you click on, and other similar interactions with our websites and apps.

To help us deliver relevant advertising using cookies, we use Google products including Google Marketing Platform. You can find out more [here](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/?_ga=2.118758602.2139151997.1537170645-1900677897.1537170645).

As mentioned in the "How We Share Your Information" section of this Policy, we participate in an advertising platform offered by our affiliate NC Audience Exchange LLC, called News IQ. To learn more about News Corp Connect please visit <http://ncaudienceexchange.com/about/>.

 **Web Beacons and Tracking Pixels**

These are bits of data that count the number of users who access a website or webpage and can also allow us to see if a cookie has been activated. Web beacons used on web pages or in emails allow us to see how successful an article has been, or whether an email message was successfully delivered and read in a marketing campaign. Web beacons are also used to verify any clicks through to links or advertisements contained in emails. We may use this information to help us identify which emails are more interesting to you and to inform advertisers how many customers have clicked on their adverts (the information shared with advertisers is aggregated and does not identify you individually).

 **Flash Cookies**

We may, in certain situations, use Adobe Flash Player to deliver special content, such as video clips or animation. To improve your user experience, Local Shared Objects (commonly known as Flash cookies) are used to provide functions such as remembering your settings and preferences. Flash cookies are stored on your device, but they are managed through an interface different from the one provided by your web browser.

 **Tracking URLs**

Tracking URLs are a special web link that allows us to measure when a link is clicked on. They are used to help us measure the effectiveness of campaigns and advertising and the popularity of articles that are read.

 **Device Fingerprinting**

We may collect and analyse a device's browser information to help identify that device, present content correctly, conduct analytics and help prevent and detect fraud.

 **If you Access our Services from a Mobile Device**

We may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geo-location data, and other transactional information for that device. We may also use the unique identifier to validate free trials, for example.

Cookies and similar technologies help us identify and prevent threats to our sites. They are necessary to protect your information and our business from outside threats.

Cookies and similar technologies permit your connection to our websites: our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, other software or hardware information, and your geographic location.

We use information about your usage of our services, websites and apps, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run, and advertisements you have seen or interacted with to assess how our services are used.

Cookies and similar technologies help us provide functionality that you need to navigate our sites, select products and services and purchase them.

The content on our websites and in our communications with you may be adjusted depending on what we know about the content, products and services that you like. This means we can highlight content and articles that we believe will be of interest to you. We provide personalisation by using cookies, IP addresses, web beacons, URL tracking and mobile app settings.

We sell space on our websites and apps to advertisers. The adverts they display on our websites will often contain cookies. Our advertisers may use cookies or similar technologies to provide you with advertisements that they believe are relevant. They may use browsing data obtained to restrict the number of times you see particular adverts (frequency capping). You may also see adverts from these advertisers on other websites you visit.

Third parties that support our services by serving advertisements or providing other services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate service usage, may also use cookies and other technologies to collect information relevant to the provision of those services.

We do not control third party cookies or other technologies. Their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. You should make sure you are aware of how third parties will use cookies by checking the third party's cookie policy.

To learn more about controlling cookies and similar technologies, please see the section below on Managing Cookies.

By downloading our apps, we will require access to the following services on your device: unique identifier (UDID), MAC address or other applicable device identifier and location. Other services may also be required in order for the apps to function. We may use this information to validate free trials. Our apps may also provide push notifications to your device. You may control these through using the tools on your device, such as turning off push notification and location services.

When you visit our websites, our partners will set cookies and similar technologies on your browser in order to help us make the sites work, analyse site usage, deliver adverts and personalise your experience. Where these partners are acting on our behalf, they are called data processors and must only act on our instructions. We will have a contract with them and they must protect your information properly. They'll use your information in accordance with this Cookie Policy and you'll be able to opt-out.

Where other partners are placing cookies and similar technologies for their own purposes, they are called data controllers and will use your information for their own purposes.

When you visit our sites you'll see notices about the use of cookies by us and our partners. You'll be able to learn more about the specific cookies in use and how to control them. By using our sites, you understand that cookies and similar technologies are used and acknowledge that by continuing to use the site, you consent to their placement.

In the future we plan to release improved controls to allow you to choose which partners can collect and use your information.

Most modern browsers are set to accept cookies by default, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser.

In addition to being able to control cookies by changing the settings in your browser on your computer, or in your mobile device's settings, you can also control which companies can set cookies and similar technologies on your devices, by visiting the following links (you'll need to turn any cookie or ad blockers off for the control pages to show which companies you can opt-out of):

  * Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB) Your Online Choices website provides more information about controlling cookies. It also provides an easy way to opt-out of behavioural advertising from each (or all) of the networks represented by the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>. 
  * The Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) control page allows you to control behavioural advertising from each of the ad networks represented by the NAI.
  * The Digital Advertising Alliance's self-regulatory program for online behavioural advertising control page allows you to control behavioural advertising from the ad networks it represents.
  * The News IQ website provides more information, and an easy way to opt-out.
  * Importantly, these ad networks set cookies to remember that you have chosen to opt-out. If you clear your cache the opt-outs will not be applied and you would need to opt-out again.

You can prevent web beacons from tracking your activity, although you won't be able to decline receiving them in emails. For information about managing your cookie options, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

Please note that by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain features, content, or personalisation available on our websites or apps.

From time to time we make changes to this Policy. This may be in relation to changes in the law, best practice, changes in our services or treatment of your personal information. Where necessary, we will notify you of these changes. We will always display clearly when the privacy policy was last amended on the website.

In addition to any general data protection enquiries you may have, you can use these details to contact our Data Protection Officer.

**Email**  

**By Post**  
Data Protection Enquiries,  
Customer Services Department,  
News UK,  
1 London Bridge Street, London, SE1 9GF
